<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Continuous-Learning on Ramunas Nognys</title>
    <link>http://localhost:58628/tags/continuous-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Continuous-Learning on Ramunas Nognys</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:58628/tags/continuous-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Art and Science of DevOps Career Development: A Systems Thinking Approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:58628/posts/pdp-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:58628/posts/pdp-example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[!info This comprehensive guide introduces a systems-based approach to DevOps career development, integrating technical mastery with cultural understanding. Through the lens of cognitive scaffolding, we explore how to build a resilient and adaptive career framework.]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-systems-nature-of-devops-evolution&#34;&gt;The Systems Nature of DevOps Evolution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of technology operations, DevOps represents more than a career path—it embodies a &lt;em&gt;complex adaptive system&lt;/em&gt; where technical expertise interweaves with cultural transformation. This guide presents a &lt;strong&gt;cognitive scaffolding&lt;/strong&gt; approach to career development, allowing you to navigate this complexity with purpose and clarity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Career Mastery: A 12-Month Engineering Evolution Plan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:58628/posts/personal-development-plan-pdp-for-devops-sre-role-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:58628/posts/personal-development-plan-pdp-for-devops-sre-role-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:58628/images/Pasted%20image%2020250201075221.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pasted image 20250201075221.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[!info] Transform your career into DevOps/SRE with this comprehensive 12-month development plan. This guide combines technical skill acquisition with cultural understanding, providing a structured pathway from foundational knowledge to advanced implementation. Perfect for engineers seeking a methodical approach to DevOps mastery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-strategic-path-to-devops-excellence&#34;&gt;The Strategic Path to DevOps Excellence&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving tech landscape, the journey to becoming a DevOps engineer requires more than just technical prowess. This comprehensive guide outlines a strategic 12-month transformation plan, combining essential technical skills with crucial cultural understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
